Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
2 gunman have been shot dead after
a firing in a shopping center in England.
As many as 80.000 residence of the city have
fled their homes to escape the shooting at...
Government forces in the southern Philippine
have launch an offense against the rebels
since fighting escalates in this
part of Asia's largest Catholic country.
A national day of mourning in the Philippine.
after 44 police commandos were killed
in the line of duty when an
anti-terror operation went wrong.
200 heavily armed separatists from the
National Liberation Front attacked the city...
The officers from the Police Special Action Force
were Killed during an operation
to capture one of the
most wanted terrorist...
PUNJAB PROVINCE
50 miles north of Lahore. PAKISTAN
Philippine authorities now say
the toll in yesterday's hotel bombing
has risen to 146 dead
and 231 wounded.
It is the most devastating terrorist
attack in Asia. in 10 years.
And the worst ever. in Manila.
While no organization has taken
responsibility for the blast.
Western intelligence sources have identified
chemical traces that are the hallmark of
the infamous arms-dealer. Aarmir Barkawi
International security experts say
that the Barkawi family
is now instigating violence
in remote capitals
To foster instability. and thus fuel
massive arms sales around the globe.
There he is.
Kamran.
Raza.
Did Philippine Intelligence track you?
Father.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
We need to discuss Major General Rahmad.
It's your sister's wedding.
I'm sorry. this can't wait.
| think your ISI officer was compromised.
Kamran.
all Pakistani intelligence
officers are compromised.
One of our Afghani friends discovered
a German BND agent in his circle.
And?
That particular general won't be
very useful to us anymore.
He's been eliminated.
Thought you might want to know.
Don't forget his family.
Vengeance must always be profound.
and absolute.
Very happy.
"BARKAWI ON SITE"
CREECH Air Force Base.
NEVADA
Pentagon just received target
confirmation from MI-6 ground missile.
You're free to execute.
Hell of a a presidential race. sir
Everyday is the same damn joke.
Seriously?
What the hell are
you made out of?
Bourbon and poor choices.
You pick a name yet?
Well. we were thinking Benjamin
if it was a boy.
- Really?
- Hell. no!!
- Ha ha ha!
- If it's a girl. maybe.
Voig ht.
You want to run
him over for me?
Believe me. sir.
We tried.
Baby.
Babe.
What?
A little problem in the nursery.
Alright. so 6 cameras. right?
One. two. three.
four. five. six.
- Why is that too much?
- Yeah. maybe.
Yeah. it's too much.
and I thought that.
They're baby gifts from the guys.
- I'll take them down.
- All we need.
- is one baby monitor.
- One baby monitor. right.
Okay.
- And a Kevlar mattress.
- and a Kevlar mattress.
Come here.
- Unhand me.
- Never.
And guess who just
got the next week off.
Oh. don't toy with me. young man.
cause there will be consequences.
We're finishing this nursery.
| can't believe it's taking me this long.
Paint samples.
- What?
- Yeah.
Oh. I got to show you
these amazing paint samples.
- Can I get a shower first?
- Not yet.
Re: Resignation
Dear Sir
| regret to inform you that
| hereby tender my resignation
from the United States Security Service
Presidential Protection Division.
It has been an honor
and a privilege.
Sir. Speaker of the House is waiting.
and the Senate Majority Leader
would like five of your time.
Ahh. hmm.
I'll take him first.
When is Trumbull getting back?
The Vice-President has
3 more days of vacation
and insinuated considerable violence
if he heard my voice before then.
Never get between
that man and a fish.
- Sir. I got your son on video-chat.
- Excellent.
- He had his first date last night.
- Mr. President.
you need to take this. sir.
Sir. Speaker of the House?
You need to take this now. sir.
This is the President.
Okay. thank you.
Sources confirmed that
Prime Minister James Wilson
has died while sleeping in his
residence at 10 Downey Street.
He is believed to have
suffered a heart attack.
Possibly. from complications
after the surgical procedure
to repair his knee a day earlier.
An autopsy has been scheduled
within the next 48 hours.
To determine the actual cause of death.
It's the White House.
It's okay.
My mom can come over.
LONDON
70 WHITEHALL
THE CABINET OFFICE
What we are proposing is that the
funeral takes place this Thursday.
this Thursday. the 9th.
4:00 PM. at St. Paul's.
The confirm attendees are all world leaders.
with the lone exception
of the Russian president.
Well. no love lost there.
Our royal family will attend the private
services in St. James's Palace the morning of
with 28 other heads of state
from all over the globe.
As per foreign royals.
Prince Albert of Monaco.
Queen Rania of Jordan.
Saudi Prince Mugrin.
Yes. it's a logistical nightmare.
But let's make sure this runs
without a hitch.
Questions?
And what special requests did
the yank circus demand so far?
Dallas Cowboys cheerleaders.
part of the ratherly possibly?
That's a request I can live with.
I'm partial to the Kardashians. myself.
As apparently as Her Majesty.
19 special requests from
12 different countries.
We denied all of them.
Any issues or special concern
with our current assessment?
We all know about he 350
or so British nationals who
traveled back and forth
to Syria in the past year.
As we've seen before in Iraq.
and Afghanistan.
Our rising concern is the handful
we believe to be former military.
- Is any of this actionable?
- No.
Very well.
And we will certify
our dear friend James.
with dignity.
Give him a ceremony he deserves.
Sir.
- Are you ready for us?
- Yeah. come on in.
Take a seat.
What are you guys
so damn nervous about?
The Brits are world-class.
We all know their reputation.
But still.
these are the trips I hate.
Last minute. out of the country.
no time to plan.
Are you sure I can't
talk you out of this?
Lynn. it's a state funeral.
They're our oldest. strongest ally.
Alright. I spent half the night
on the line with our advance team.
Metropolitan Police will secure the parameter
of the funeral at St. Paul's Cathedral.
Air Force One will land
at Stansted Airport.
On the ground.
it's all Mike.
Touch down.
Then a 12-minute chopper
ride to Somerset House.
From there we take
an armored vehicle escort
down Sweet Street.
to the Cathedral.
You don't seem thrilled.
The British have their hands full.
It's a cluster-fuck.
Sir.
Well.
40 different countries.
with 40 different security teams.
Minimal flexibility on approach routes.
funeral seating. egress.
- Can we make it work?
- Mike?
| always do. sir.
Good.
| know it's not great timing
for you. but...
It's what I do.
Thank you sir.
VICE PRESIDENT
ALLAN TRUMBULL
- There's my man.
- Mr. Vice-President.
- How was your vacation. sir?
- Son.
Do you have any idea.
the joy a man feels
pulling a 70 pound king mackerel
out of the waters around Jekyll Island?
- No. sir. I don't.
- That makes two of us.
And I have to wait until
next year to find out.
But.
thanks for asking.
Oh. yeah. that's in Sinai.
- It's beautiful.
- There you go.
Jeez. it's incredible.
| love these things. they...
Don't worry about a thing.
we'll be fine.
- Doris. can we have a minute?
- Sure.
- Oh you meant Leah. Right.
- Very funny. Doris.
She tells me not to worry.
It's only 3 days.
- Yeah.
- And I'm not due for 2 weeks.
I'm not walking away.
quite so easy this time.
Hey.
| got this.
You go and you do what
you have to do. and
we will be right here
when you get back.
Okay?
You.
say bye bye to Daddy.
Bye bye. Daddy.
Bell tolls.
Yeah.
| love you
You better.
Behave.
- Ah. here you go.
- Thank you.
You've been haddled lately.
You've been busy nesting?
- Something like that.
- Mm. hmm.
Your idea of nesting being.
bullet-proofing the walls of the nursery?
Now. that is actually a great idea.
Yes.
I'll do it.
Well. that only took 2 weeks.
Uh-uh.
That's no small thing being a god-mother.
| mean.
| didn't take your asking lightly.
Oh. I know.
You think you can handle it?
Well. I'm competent. brilliant.
stunningly beautiful. and really fun. aren't I.
Really honored.
Thank you. Lynn.
NEW SCOTLAND YARD
8:30 AM
- Big day ahead?
- Correction. make a day.
Morning.
Thank you.
- Good morning. sir.
- Morning. sir.
Just your signature here.
Thank you. sir.
Gentlemen.
Ladies.
Today. I need your undivided best.
The most important people in
the world are in our care.
So muck in. and get it right.
Always. chief.
Good morning. London.
STANSTED AIRPORT
20 MILES NORTH OF LONDON
230 PM
Southpaw has landed.
- Agent Banning. John Lancaster. MI-5.
- Hey. John.
- A bit early. aren't you?
- Nope.
- We're moving up our schedule.
- I see.
The fewer people know the President's
exact movements. the better.
- Why wasn't I told?
- Nobody was.
That's how you keep it a surprise.
Thanks for the help.
ST PAUL'S CATHEDRAL
300 PM
With security at unprecedented levels.
in anticipation of the funeral.
set to begin just an hour from now
this isn't just the gathering
of the world's most powerful leaders.
It is the most protected event on earth.
Rooftop. in position.
All units in position.
Marine Force 1. 2. and 3 on
final approach to Somerset House.
Marine 1 cleared for landing.
SOMERSET HOUSE
BUCKINGHAM PALACE
GERMAN CHANCELLOR
AGNES BRUCKNER
Manni. it's okay.
Thank you
Yeah. I understand.
Yeah. I promise.
Everything is going to be fine.
Important matters of state?
That was daughter number 2.
She didn't pass
her driving test.
Guess whose fault it is?
JAPANESE PRIME MINISTER
TSUTOMU NAKUSHIMA
How much longer?
We are almost there. sir.
I'm sorry but as expected...
...there are heavy security measures.
WESTMINSTER ABBEY
315 PM
ITALIAN PRIME MINISTER
ANTONIO GUSTO
| can't believe we're doing this...
...a private tour of Westminster Abbey...
...just for you.
| only turn 30 once.
FRENCH PRESIDENT
JACQUES MAINARD
It's time. Mr. President
The cars are ready?
But not too ready...
Wait 10 minutes?
At least.
Southpaw has arrived at destination.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Bugs the shit out of me.
Thank you.
- Sir.
- Thank you. Mike.
Thank you very much. Lynn.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
- Good to see you.
Benjamin. thank you for coming.
- We're grateful you could make it.
- I'm sorry.
You know. the funny thing is.
James always hated funerals.
Yeah. don't we all.
Get down!
Mike!
Move!
Let's get inside!
Okay.
- Alright. back to the car.
- Okay.
Grenade!
Get down!
Let's go.
We've been compromised.
Fuck.
They're not real cops!
Two in front!
Golf 1 to Cat team.
Support on me now!
- You okay? - Yeah.
- Yeah!
Stay with me.
we'll get you out of here.
GET DOWN!
- Shit.
- Damn it. Mike.
What's going on?
- Oh my. why all of a sudden?
- Oh my god...
Mr. President!
We have to evacuate.
Oh. Jesus.
There's been a massive
attack at the Cathedral.
- Chelsea bridge has collapsed.
- So is Westminster Abbey.
- Get me a circuit in counter-terror.
- Yes. sir.
Where's Emergency Response?
On their way. sir.
Voight. where the fuck are you?
Almost there.
Move!
You okay sir?
- Keep you head down.
- Get inside!
Get inside!
Mike!
- Let's go!
- Mike!
Go. go!
Let's get to the chopper.
Dean Court.
Black Land Rover.
| don't believe it.
They overran everything.
Not everything.
Looking for hot extract.
Marine 1 for Southpaw.
Fuck.
Comms are down.
Alright. here we go.
Get down!
- Voight.
- Yeah.
Let them drive next to us.
- Copy that.
- Hold him.
Hold him.
Now!
Voight. hard brake. now!
Drive!
Come on!
Get down.
Get down!
Voight!
- Voight.
Keep pressure on the wound.
- Voight!
- Voight! Voight!
- He's dead. Lynn.
- Oh god.
Get down. sir.
- Jacobs. take that wheel.
- Got it!
- Get in!
- Got it.
Mike. on your left!
Not really where you
want to be right now.
- Fuck you!
- Fuck me?
Fuck you.
We're almost there sir.
Come on. let's go.
Go. sir. go.
5 world leaders are confirmed dead.
Along with hundreds of innocent civilians
in an attack that has decimated most of the
known landmarks in the British capital.
SANA'A
YEMEN
Clarkson and Asher are alive.
All the rest are dead.
And I thought it was
too much to hope for.
We just changed the world.
Plan B. Sultan.
Fate. has smiled on us.
CENTRAL LONDON
Lights out. London.
Generators will kick in.
Ladies and gentlemen. good evening.
We've asked the residents of London
to stay indoors for their own safekeeping.
While the situation remains fluid.
let there be no doubt.
that every relevant police authority
and counter-terrorism unit
is actively at work regaining
control of our streets.
- And within hours we will secure the city.
- Call Mike.
And those responsible.
would be swiftly brought to justice.
Jesus. it's not connecting.
- How bad is it?
- It's pretty goddamn bad. sir.
All lines of communication
have been compromised.
- both civilian and military.
- Shit.
We've tasked satellites and drones
to get eyes on. but so far nothing.
Sir. the drone is on station.
We have visuals incoming.
Coming up.
Oh my god.
SECRETARY OF DEFENSE
RUTH MACMILLAN
DEPUTY DIRECTOR NSA
RAY MONROE
Nearest Quick Reaction Force?
- Sicily. two hours out.
- Speed them up.
And get a line to Downing Street.
and to Box Emergency Command.
Yes. sir.
Satellite is up.
Marine One is airborne.
Southpaw is evaced.
- Good lord.
- Yes!
Marine One with Southpaw on board.
en route to Stansted.
Prep Air Force One for urgent departure.
Copy.
Air Force One prepped and ready to go.
It was a trap.
That's an understatement.
Holy shit.
It's one thing to plan for this.
Another to live it.
Alright. well. we're good now.
- It'll be okay.
- Yeah.
We'll be on secure ground
in 10 minutes. okay?
There was no chatter on this.
None.
Something of this magnitude.
it took years to plan
and we had days.
It's a fucking bloodbath.
How did they do this. Mike?
They only have to
get it right once.
Today. they got it right
way more than that.
Oh fuck!
Mayday! Mayday!
Mayday!
Marine Three is down.
Oh no.
Roof-top. 3 o'clock.
you see him?
Marine Two.
2 shooters at 3 o'clock.
Copy that.
- We're being pinged.
- Stingers.
Deploying flares.
Okay. stinger down.
- Stinger at 3 o'clock.
- Climb! Climb!
- Marine One. out of flares.
- Marine Two. out of flares.
- Marine Two. prepare for sacrifice.
- Copy.
Marine Two is down.
Missile lock on.
Mr. President. we're going to take a hit.
Brace for impact.
Oh god.
Sir.
Sir. you good?
You okay?
Sit up.
Can you move?
Yeah.
Okay. sir.
- You with me?
- Yeah.
Lynn!
No.
- My god.
- Oh my god.
Ben.
Ben. get out of the chopper.
This thing could blow at any second.
Go.
| never thought you would outlive me.
Me either.
Oh shit.
Do me a favor.
Stay alive.
You got to see your kid.
Make those fuckers pay.
| will.
Fox to command.
This is Golf 1. you copy?
Fuck.
Looks like we're walking.
Mr. President.
Those better be comfortable shoes.
Sir. I think you're going to
want to take a look at this.
I'll put it up.
To our friends in the west.
whose idea of war
is a remote testing location.
Thousands of miles from the
comfort zone of your shopping malls.
who sent your porge to be blown
to bits in our land. or better yet.
Murder our family remotely from the sky.
Your time. is over.
We're bringing the war to you.
Make no mistake.
This is the day.
when your world changes forever.
Jesus.
This is all over social media too.
Everybody in the world has seen this.
Aamir Barkawi.
Number 6 on the 10 list.
This man is responsible for
more deaths than the Plague.
Sells arms to every failed state
in the world.
Has a vast array of connections.
terrorists. mercenaries. corporations.
Mr. Vice-President.
it's Barkawi.
Put him through.
Thought you might take my call.
You understand if I make
it difficult to track.
You have me at somewhat of a loss.
| thought you would've learned a lesson
by now. about crawling out of your hole.
I've never lifted
a finger against you.
You arm those who have.
| sold triggers. Mr. Trumbull.
just like you.
What do you want?
Your President.
You can end this right now.
- Just hand him over.
- That's not going to happen.
Then every death from this moment
forward will be on your hand.
Barkawi. sells arms
to dummy companies.
Some of them probably in London.
Find a connection to him.
He's probably been
planning this for years.
Everybody makes a mistake.
We have to find him before
he finds the President.
Let's get to it.
- Mike. he's a policeman.
- Yeah?
Not exactly standard police issue.
Really?
Oh. my god.
- I've never seen a man suffocate before.
- I didn't have a knife.
He's got more ammunition
than the entire US Army.
How can they pull
something like this off.
There's got to be somebody
on the inside.
Yeah. looks like it.
These aren't you typical
spring pre-hillbillies.
- These guys are pros.
- We should go for the Embassy.
Nah.
They'll be expecting that.
There's a MI-6 safe house near here.
| have a contact there.
We go there. we wait it out.
and we get an extraction.
- Do you trust them?
- Yeah.
The fact is. every single one of these guys
is a terrorist asshole until proven otherwise.
The only person you trust right now.
is me. okay?
Come on. let's go.
We got to get underground.
These guys are everywhere.
Let's go.
Just stay here.
I'll be back.
Raza.
Here.
Oh. we can do this.
it's really fun.
Raza.
Answer me. brother.
Raza's not feeling too well at the moment.
He's a little bit fucked up.
Hey. you.
What's this dick guy's name?
This is Kamran.
Who is this?
Hey. Cameron.
My name is Mike Banning.
- You are the one with the President.
- Bingo.
So why don't you boys pack
up your shit and head back
to Fuckingninstan or wherever
it is you're from.
You should've let us
Kill him quickly.
Because now. we're going
to kill him slowly.
And stream it live.
For the whole world to see.
Can you hear me. Mr. President?
- Tell him.
- Yeah. he can hear you.
Hey. here's something
| want you hear first.
That's the sound of
your brother dying.
Yeah.
Not much of a talker. that one.
But I bet you.
one of your men will.
I'll see you soon. Cameron.
- Was that really necessary?
- No.
The Brits are compromised.
Police for sure.
Who do you trust?
We can also assume all communications
are compromised.
Anything that isn't secured.
could get into the wrong hands. sir.
- And Banning would know that too.
- So how could he even reach out for help?
There. freeze that.
Sir.
Is Banning left-handed?
No. right-handed.
Okay. well. the President doesn't move
without a drone or a satellite over his head.
- Banning knows that.
- It's his left hand.
- Southpaw. six.
- Shorthand for MI-6.
Look for any MI-6 location
in that area.
- Yes. sir.
- Alright. Banning.
- You okay?
- Oh. Yeah.
Made out of Bourbon
and bad choices. huh?
Sit down. take deep breaths.
How many you think died?
| don't know.
A lot.
All those innocent people.
Dead.
because of me.
No.
Not because of you. because of them.
They tried to kill you. sir.
And they killed
all these people.
just to make everyone
else a little more afraid.
Well. fuck that.
And fuck them.
Mike.
You don't let them take me.
- I'm not going to.
- You need to do it.
If it comes to it.
If it's going south.
-Sir.
-Mike.
If it comes to I.
| want you to kill me.
That's an order.
| will not be executed for propaganda
as my son and
the American people see me
on fucking YouTube
for the rest of their lives.
Okay.
Vice President Trumbull.
it's an honor. sir.
Chief inspector.
I'm afraid our...
news isn't promising.
Our dearly departed Prime Minister
James Wilson was assassinated.
Poison in his anesthesia.
and his doctor's body found
dumped about an hour ago.
State funeral.
Must-attend event for western leaders.
Each one a target.
Goddamn.
And we walked right into it.
And all dead.
By your men and ours.
What's happening on the ground?
Well. the terrorists have
killed 19 first-responders.
With another 30 unaccounted for.
They're impersonating us.
Our people are walking
right into ambushes.
Say the word and we go in.
But make no mistake.
We risk turning London
into another Fallujah.
That's the last thing we need.
The President in the
middle of an urban battle.
Or the citizens of London.
Or you're just as likely to take out
half the Metropolitan Police Force.
unless you can tell me
how you can tell the difference
between the good
guys and the bad guys.
We're going to have to
stand down our Emergency Services.
- Surrender London?
- He's right.
Take out all legitimate personnel.
Anyone that remains
is a terrorist.
Look. the sooner we end this.
the more chance there is of stopping
London becoming a complete war zone.
Well. how do we get the
word out to our people?
Air raid system.
We sound that. people know to
stay secure in their place. then...
you let the military sweep in.
Knock door-to-door. if necessary.
Clear these bastards out.
6:30 PM
(Air raid alarm)
Good evening.
Is the Auntie in?
Put that away.
- Are you who I think you are?
- Unfortunately.
Thanks.
What a pleasure this is. two handsome men
visiting me on such a lovely evening.
Long time. Jax.
Yeah. not long enough.
Mr. President.
Sir.
Jacquelin. MI-6 finest.
- Don't fuck with her.
- Hello.
The phones are down.
That said. it did allow us
to pick up this.
Mr. President. Banning.
| hope this finds you well.
Mike. we got your message.
And I'm sure you don't know
who you can trust.
and all prior authentications
may be compromised.
So. I offer you this.
Do you have any idea the joy
a man experiences
pulling a 70 pound King Mackerel
- out of the waters around Jekyll Island?
That's him.
A Delta Team has been
clandestinely inserted.
By now. they should be
en route to your position.
They'll take you to the US Embassy.
where an armored convoy stands by
to get you out of SAM range.
- And on to a military train.
- Thank god.
Let's get us out of here.
Alright.
Sir. who's behind all this?
Aamir Barkawi.
Barkawi provides armaments.
He's a fucking criminal.
Shielded by governments.
Mike. there was a drone
strike. to get him.
2 years ago. authorized by the G8.
So we took a shot.
He survived.
We didn't know his family was there.
His daughter was killed.
Well. he certainly got his revenge.
Civilians?
Well. if they're not being
targeted specifically...
- Collateral damage?
- Yeah. quite a lot. I'm afraid.
It's government targeted. No official support
from any countries Barkawi show. but..
Didn't have any problems
finding recruits. did he?
It's United Nations with every fucking
blood on their hands.
Who's on the inside?
There's got to be somebody.
Yeah. you're right.
They've infiltrated our CCTV system.
They might copied internet
outside the network.
- Yeah. but who?
- I don't know.
Mike.
if you hadn't move our schedule up.
Here you go. sir.
- Get this down in you.
- Thanks.
| don't know about you.
but I'm thirsty as fuck.
Yeah.
How're you doing?
| was thinking about my son.
He sends me these
jokes every day.
It's kind of our.
our thing. you know.
A little off-color.
His mother wouldn't approve. but...
| tell you something. Mike.
These little messages
| get from him everyday.
They mean everything. you'll see.
Most important thing.
never criticize.
always encourage.
You just want them to be passionate.
That's what I always tell my son.
Find something you care about.
and care deeply.
That and the Golden Rule.
Treat others as you like to be treated.
That's it?
Yeah. basically.
What about all the other stuff.
Sleeping. eating. electrical outlets.
diapers. stairs. and ...
That stuff takes care of itself.
- Really?
You'll figure it out.
| think your dates have arrived.
When did Trumbull leave that message?
6:13
32 minutes.
No way they got here that fast.
- Where's the zoom in?
- Here.
They're not sweating.
- Huh?
- That gear weighs 40 pounds.
They just stalked all the way from outside
the wire and not a drop of sweat?
It's got to be them.
Now they're going around the back.
This doesn't look like a rescue formation.
Please don't tell me
that's not our Delta team.
They've intercepted Trumbull's message.
Jax.
where's the armory?
Go.
- You're not coming?
- They'll have this place surrounded.
They catch us in the open.
we're done.
They're not looking for you.
Go.
- Find the mole.
- Right.
The wheels are in
the garage downstairs.
Alright.
Point this end towards the bad guy.
This is not good. Mike.
Stay in here.
Stay down.
And anybody but me
opens that door.
- you empty that into him.
- What if you don't come back?
You're fucked.
- Mike.
- Don't jinx me.
That was inspiring.
| was wondering when you're
going to come out of the closet.
That's not funny.
We're almost out of this. sir.
I'm a man of my own. am [|?
Okay. let's go.
- God bless MI-6.
- I'll drive. you shoot.
What the fuck are you doing here?
- We have a mole.
- I know.
Well. any ideas?
Someone who likely has access to everything.
Routes. Security protocols.
Emergency circuits.
Jacquelin.
What brings you here?
7-30 PM
- Do we have the Embassy covered?
- Affirmative. brother.
Double the men. I want every
single man on that perimeter.
The car is bullet proof.
not politician proof.
Hey.
The president of the United States
hasn't driven a car in 6 years.
- What do you want?
- Fuck.
Take a left.
- Where're we going. Mike?
- The Embassy.
The Embassy.
- You said they're expecting me.
- Yeah.
But. we're shit out of options.
Here. take a right.
Mr. Vice President. you wanted us
to find Barkawi's mistake.
Take a look at this.
Of the 119 known Barkawi front companies
he's used in the past.
28 of them located in the UK.
11 in London proper.
- But. that's not news.
- But. it is a base line.
Now. every entity he's
ever used in the past
followed a very rough
communication pattern. except...
No known communication
in or out ever.
That's under construction.
No one lives or works there.
That's why this is
particularly interesting.
| had my NSA analysts take
a peek at the power usage.
Through the roof
for the last 3 weeks.
Pretty odd. considering nobody
lives or works there.
Central London.
Right under our bloody noses.
Tell SAS that we're going
to make a house call.
Right.
It doesn't feel right.
Slow.
Left.
Okay. stop.
This doesn't look good. Mike.
There's no way to
dress this up. sir.
- It isn't good.
- Could be worse.
We could be walking.
Atta boy.
Don't stop for anyone.
Fuck!
- Are we clear?
- Yeah.
- We fucking made it.
- We did.
We did.
Mike!
Where is he?
Fuckers.
Broadwick and Lexington stop.
Leave him.
Come on. back off.
Take it easy. take it easy.
You got to be Banning.
Will Davis.
Captain. 22 SAS.
Trumbull sent us.
called Jacquelin.
President Asher has just been taken.
And these assholes.
intend to publicly execute him.
We know. at 8:00 PM.
It's all over the internet.
We'll take care of that.
Move out!
Hey. hey. wait.
Look. we can't let you
come with us. mate.
How many times
you've saved this man's ass?
Now. I'm going to go get him.
And you can either kill me.
or you can come with me.
| ain't going to go
any other way.
After you.
AUTHORISATION CODE DISABLED CCTV
NETWORK CONNECTION IN PROGRESS
CCTV is back up.
What did you do?
Disable the authorization code
that shut down the CCTV system.
They've been watching us
using our own surveillance systems.
Wait.
What authorization code?
7-50 PM
You should be thankful.
How many men get to experience
their death witnessed by billions.
...live.
You are going to
go down in history.
I'm not the only one who's
going to die today. Kamran.
Box Command.
Banning.
Mike Banning? Chief Inspector Hazard.
Scotland Yard. Hold your position.
Our military will be on
your location in 20 minutes.
No sir. The President's
going to be dead in 10.
You don't understand.
We have NSA imagery of
where you're going.
It's their base of operations.
There are nearly a 100 terrorists in there.
Yeah. Well. They should
have brought more men.
- Things are going to get sporty.
- Just watch your balls.
Will do.
RPG!
2 o'clock clear!
Move up!
Okay.
Fuck that.
It's fucking like trapped
in a storm blasting.
We can't storm that villa
with our force so small.
Yeah. they kill the President
the second we try it.
Alright.
Call Box Command.
Make sure the utilities here
- ...are isolated and switch off.
- You sounded like it's part of a plan.
- See the generator?
- Yeah.
- Let's poke out their eyes.
- Yeah. Generator. 12 o'clock.
- Fuck.
- What happened?
The power supply was just cut.
Get the emergency generators up.
Come on!
Mike.
This is what we got.
This is a 3-story building.
The entry point is here.
There are two stairwells.
One here. and one here.
We believe the President is
being held in this room.
on the second floor.
Hold your position.
| need you to hit this building
with everything you got.
- You got it.
- Keep them busy. I'll sneak in solo.
Take that.
Do not touch that
button until I tell you.
- Are you fucking crazy?
- Yeah.
Wish me luck.
Don't shoot me.
FLAMMABLE GAS
755 PM
They're almost here.
Why don't you just kill him now?
No!
The whole world has to see this.
You hear that. Kamran? That's
the sound of inevitability.
I'm going to kill you live.
But that doesn't mean
you can't suffer privately first.
Look at me!
| held my sister
as she died in my arms.
We're all monsters. Mr. President.
It won't justify your insanity
to make you better about yourself.
Shoot him!
757 PM
7-59 PM
Almost.
The power is back. we're
waiting for the internet connection.
Come on.
Technology. only as good as
the dumbshits that are using it.
- How long?
- Seconds.
- We are live now.
- Okay.
Say hello to the world.
Mr. President.
8:00 PM
Oh my god.
Any last words. Mr. President?
| do solemnly swear.
that I will faithfully execute the office
of the President of the United States.
Son of a bitch.
...the United States.
and will to the best of my ability.
preserve. protect and defend...
Oh my god.
I'm not watching this.
You know what
you guys don't get?
We're not a fucking building.
We're not a fucking flag.
We're not just one man!
Assholes like you.
have been trying to kill us
for a long fucking time.
But you know what?
A thousand years from now.
We'll still fucking be here.
Mike!
Grenade!
What took you so long?
Sorry. I had a couple
of errands to run.
Shit. does this fucker ever die?
Alright. we got to go.
- You good?
- Let's get the hell out of here.
Go!
Move. move. move...!
Mike!
Come on!
Damn it.
I'm out.
I'm out too.
Come in!
- Davis.
- We're trapped!
| repeat. we are trapped!
- Blow it!
Are you insane?
| can't blow it yet. you're not out.
We're not gonna get out
unless you do!
Trust me!
Now. god damn it!
Go. go. go!
Banning.
Banning. do you copy?
- Has anyone found any sign of him?
- Nothing. over.
Negative.
Okay. Well. stay sharp.
Keep looking.
Box command.
No sign of the President yet.
Box Command.
we found them.
The President is alive.
- Yay!
- Yeah!
Have I ever tell you.
| fucking hate funerals.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Sir. I got you.
Mr. President.
Funny.
Is that all they got?
Yeah. it looks like it.
Lieutenant.
this could be the missing link.
to Barkawi.
I'll get it to
Box Command right away
Next time I tell you to blow it.
just blow it.
- Good job. Lieutenant.
- You too. Banning.
Safe journey home.
If that's possible for you.
Next time. you want to leave town
after betraying your country.
how about you steal a car.
to take you to your get away vehicle.
Perhaps you want one without a GPS.
Because that just takes all the fun out of it.
You forgot to delete you access logs.
Your authorization code is there.
bright as day.
The security cameras
showed you logging on.
Get on the floor.
Do I have to tell you.
this is the most dangerous time
since the Great War.
We're cutting budgets while
the barbarians are at the gate.
The system's failing us. Jax.
it's broken.
You know it as well as I do.
Things have to change
So you think
you teach us all a lesson?
That and 20 million Euros.
Come with me. Jax.
Get on the fucking floor.
Don't.
Get on the floor.
Get on the floor. John.
Get on the fucking floor!
Sir.
Your call phone.
Kamran?
Mr. Barkawi.
| thought you'd take my call.
You see this war.
this war which you started.
You think it's over?
I'm dedicating my
life to your deaths.
This war will not end.
Maybe you should look out your window.
Clear to proceed
Ground asset confirmed.
Target clear of civilian persons.
2 weeks after the devastating
attacks on the British capital.
a new government has been installed.
and the city. has begun to rebuild.
In the words of Prime Minister Clarkson:
"London may have fallen. but it has
always endured. and will rise again.”
So Daddy is going to be
taking some more time off.
isn't that cool?
Yeah. maybe it's the new me.
Or maybe the President insisted.
Yeah.
He says he reckons I've
earned a few days off.
Thanks to you. little one.
It's okay. baby.
It's okay.
| wonder what you're going to
be passionate about with?
Yeah.
Our hearts go out
to the people of London.
and to our friends around the world.
Far too many people died
for no good reason.
There are those who will say that
this would never have happened
if we would just
mind our own business.
Nothing could be further from the truth.
Frankly. we live in a dangerous
world and we have few good options.
But the worst option.
is to do nothing.
And finally.
We owe it to our children.
and to their children.
to engage in the world.
God bless you all.
And god bless the
United States of America.
That was vice President Trumbull...
[Delete]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm